<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors on Matthew D. Hirschey</title>
    <link>/authors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Authors on Matthew D. Hirschey</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	    <atom:link href="/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Matthew Hirschey is a tenured Associate Professor at Duke University in the Departments of Medicine, Division of Endocrinology, Metabolism and Nutrition and Pharmacology &amp;amp; Cancer Biology, and is a faculty member of the Duke Molecular Physiology Institute where his lab is located.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His scientific interests include studying how cells integrate nutrient sensing and metabolism. He is particularly interested in understanding how metabolites and chemical modifications control metabolism. Metabolic regulation is important for several physiological states and disease processes, including diabetes, cardiovascular disease, cancer, and the aging process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His work has appeared in several leading journals, including Nature, Science, Cell Metabolism and Molecular Cell. He has received numerous awards including an Innovator Award from the American Heart Association, a New Scholar in Aging Award from the Ellison Medical Foundation, the Helmholtz Young Investigator in Diabetes (HeIDi) Award, and the Glenn Award.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He received a degree in Biological Sciences from the University of Vermont, and a Ph.D. in Chemistry and Biochemistry from the University of California, Santa Barbara. He was a post-doctoral research fellow at the Gladstone Institutes at the University of California in San Francisco.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
